Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXXI. SYSTEM BOARDS
  - Sub-Series 250-116. System Boards. Oregon-Washington Railroad and Navigation Company
    - Oregon-Washington Railroad and Navigation Company System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1948 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-117. System Boards. Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1963 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1952-1960 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1935-1951 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1933 (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-118. System Boards. New York, New Haven, and Hartford
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford System Board of Adjustment (Subject: Appeal John J. Collins), 1961 (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1959 (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1954 (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1944 (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford System Board of Adjustment, 1925-1933 (Box 210, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 250-119. System Boards. Central Vermont
    - Central Vermont System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1965 (Box 210, Folder 15)
    - Central Vermont System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1958 (Box 210, Folder 16)
    - Central Vermont System Board of Adjustment, 1930-1945 (Box 210, Folder 17)
    - Central Vermont System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1926 (Box 210, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 250-120. System Boards. Gulf Coast Lines
    - Gulf Coast Lines System Board of Adjustment, 1964-1965 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Gulf Coast Lines System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Gulf Coast Lines System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1962 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Gulf Coast Lines System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Gulf Coast Lines System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1955 (Box 211, Folder 5)
      July 1951-55.
    - Gulf Coast Lines System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1951 (Box 211, Folder 6)
      August 1948-June 1951.
    - Gulf Coast Lines System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1948 (Box 211, Folder 7)
      1945-July 1948.
    - Gulf Coast Lines System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1944 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-121. System Boards. Southeastern Express
    - Southeastern Express System Board of Adjustment, 1928-1938 (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Southeastern Express System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1927 (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-122. System Boards. Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac
    - Consolidated System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1965 (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1959 (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1947 (Box 211, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 250-123. System Boards. Grand Trunk (Lines West)
    - Grand Trunk (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1959 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Grand Trunk (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1955 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Grand Trunk (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1937 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Grand Trunk (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1930 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-125. System Boards. Georgia
    - Georgia System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1965 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 250-126. System Boards. Gulf and Ship Island
    - Gulf and Ship Island System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1931 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 250-127. System Boards. Denver and Rio Grande Western
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1959 (Box 212, Folder 8)
      June 1958-59.
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 212, Folder 9)
      1956-May 1958.
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1955 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1952 (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1948 (Box 212, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 250-128. System Boards. Toledo, Peoria, and Western
    - Toledo, Peoria, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1958 (Box 212, Folder 13)
      May 1947-58.
    - Toledo, Peoria, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 212, Folder 14)
      1947 April
    - Toledo, Peoria, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 212, Folder 15)
      1947 March
    - Toledo, Peoria, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 213, Folder 1)
      January-February 1947.
    - Toledo, Peoria, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1946 (Box 213, Folder 2)
      September-December 1946.
    - Toledo, Peoria, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1946 (Box 213, Folder 3)
      May-August 1946.
    - Toledo, Peoria, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1946 (Box 213, Folder 4)
      February 16, 1946-April 1946.
    - Toledo, Peoria, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1946 (Box 213, Folder 5)
      December 1945-February 15, 1946.
    - Toledo, Peoria, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1929-1945 (Box 213, Folder 6)
      1929-November 1945.
  - Sub-Series 250-129. System Boards. Buffalo, Rochester, and Pittsburgh
    - Buffalo, Rochester, and Pittsburgh System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1947 (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 250-131. System Boards. Chicago, Milwaukee, and Gary
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, and Gary System Board of Adjustment, 1922 (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-132. System Boards. Seaboard Airline
    - Seaboard Airline System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1962 (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - Seaboard Airline System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 213, Folder 10)
      April 1956-58.
    - Seaboard Airline System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1956 (Box 213, Folder 11)
      February 1954-March 1956.
    - Seaboard Airline System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1954 (Box 213, Folder 12)
      October 1951-January 1954.
    - Seaboard Airline System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1951 (Box 214, Folder 1)
      1939-September 1951.
    - Seaboard Airline System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1938 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-133. System Boards. Toledo and Ohio Central
    - Toledo and Ohio Central System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1927 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-135. System Boards. New York, Ontario, and Western
    - New York, Ontario, and Western Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1941 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-138. System Boards. Lembert Point Coal Piers
    - Lembert Point Coal Piers System Board of Adjustment, 1956 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 250-139. System Boards. Nashville Terminals
    - Nashville Terminals System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1959 (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 250-140. System Boards. Virginian Railway
    - Virginian Railway System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1947 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 250-152. System Boards. Central Inspection and Weighing Bureau
    - Central Inspection and Weighing Bureau System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1941 (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-153. System Boards. A&V, VS&P
    - A&V, VS&P System Board of Adjustment, 1922 (Box 214, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 250-154. System Boards. Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1962 (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1957 (Box 214, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 250-156. System Boards. Cupples Station
    - Cupples Station System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 214, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 250-157. System Boards. Wabash
    - Wabash System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1962 (Box 214, Folder 14)
      April 10, 1958-62.
    - Wabash System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 214, Folder 15)
      1956-April 9, 1958.
    - Wabash System Board of Adjustment, 1952-1955 (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - Wabash System Board of Adjustment, 1937-1951 (Box 214, Folder 17)
    - Wabash System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1936 (Box 214, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 250-168. System Boards. Boston, Revere Beach, and Lynn
    - Boston, Revere Beach, and Lynn System Board of Adjustment, 1935-1936 (Box 214, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 250-169. System Boards. Danville and Western
    - Danville and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 214, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 250-171. System Boards. Pittsburgh and West Virginia
    - Pittsburgh and West Virginia System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1965 (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - Pittsburgh and West Virginia System Board of Adjustment, 1940-1954 (Box 214, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 250-178. System Boards. Canadian Pacific
    - Canadian Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 214, Folder 23)
    - Canadian Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1962 (Box 215, Folder 1)
      August 1961-62.
    - Canadian Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1961 (Box 215, Folder 2)
      April 1958-July 1961.
    - Canadian Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1942-1958 (Box 215, Folder 3)
      1942-March 1958.
    - Canadian Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1941 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 215, Folder 5)
      March-December 1965.
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 215, Folder 6)
      January 16, 1965-February 1965.
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1964-1965 (Box 215, Folder 7)
      1964-January 15, 1965.
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 215, Folder 8)
      October 26-30, 1964. Subject: Minutes
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1963 (Box 215, Folder 9)
      Subject: Appeal L. M. Zacharias
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1958 (Box 215, Folder 11)
      Subject: G.M. Mathieson
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1962 (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1958 (Box 215, Folder 13)
      July-December 1958.
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 216, Folder 1)
      1956-June 1958.
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1955 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1954 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1954 (Box 216, Folder 4)
      Subject: Ray N. Cameron
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1953 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1948 (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1946 (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie and Pacific Regions) System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1938 (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-180. System Boards. Columbus and Greenville
    - Columbus and Greenville System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1969 (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Columbus and Greenville System Board of Adjustment, 1932-1959 (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-181. System Boards. Lake Superior and Ishpeming
    - Lake Superior and Ishpeming System Board of Adjustment, 1924-1958 (Box 216, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-183. System Boards. Canadian National
    - Canadian National System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1962 (Box 216, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 250-187. System Boards. Ogden Union
    - Ogden Union System Board of Adjustment, 1964-1968 (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - Ogden Union System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1963 (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - Ogden Union System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1956 (Box 216, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 250-188. System Boards. Chicago Union Station
    - Chicago Union Station System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1964 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Union Station System Board of Adjustment, 1924-1960 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-192. System Boards. Northern Pacific
    - Northern Pacific Terminal Company of Oregon System Board of Adjustment, 1927-1962 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-193. System Boards. Southern Weighing and Inspection Bureau
    - Southern Weighing and Inspection Bureau System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1923 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-195. System Boards. City Bus Company
    - City Bus Company System Board of Adjustment, 1935-1959 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 250-196. System Boards. Dallas Union Terminal
    - Dallas Union Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1930-1958 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 250-211. System Boards. St. Joseph Union Depot Company
    - St. Joseph Union Depot Company System Board of Adjustment, 1935-1959 (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 250-214. System Boards. Duluth, Winnipeg, and Pacific
    - Duluth, Winnipeg, and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1958 (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-216. System Boards. Illinois Terminal
    - Illinois Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1961 (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - Illinois Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1945-1960 (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - Illinois Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1934-1944 (Box 217, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-217. System Boards. Albany Passenger Terminal
    - Albany Passenger Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1955 (Box 217, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 250-221. System Boards. Pacific Electric
    - Pacific Electric System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 217, Folder 13)
      Disbanded, effective November 1, 1965
    - Pacific Electric System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1962 (Box 217, Folder 14)
      June 13, 1956-62. Disbanded, effective November 1, 1965
    - Pacific Electric System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1956 (Box 217, Folder 15)
      1945-June 12, 1956. Disbanded, effective November 1, 1965
  - Sub-Series 250-230. System Boards. Akron, Canton, and Youngstown
    - Akron, Canton, and Youngstown System Board of Adjustment, 1937-1959 (Box 217, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 250-233. System Boards. Clinchfield
    - Clinchfield System Board of Adjustment, 1936-1960 (Box 217, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 250-234. System Boards. Alton and Southern
    - Alton and Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1937-1955 (Box 217, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 250-235. System Boards. Chicago and Illinois Western
    - Chicago and Illinois Western System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1968 (Box 217, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-236. System Boards. Canadian National Express
    - Canadian National Express System Board of Adjustment, 1935-1961 (Box 217, Folder 12)
      Consolidated with System Board No. 517, Canadian Pacific Express System Board of Adjustment, effective September 8, 1961
  - Sub-Series 250-239. System Boards. Chicago Tunnel Terminal
    - Chicago Tunnel Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1935-1959 (Box 217, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 250-241. System Boards. Canadian National Railways (Newfoundland Division)
    - Canadian National Railways (Newfoundland Division) System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1962 (Box 217, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 250-251. System Boards. Atlanta, Birmingham, and Coast Railroad
    - Atlanta, Birmingham, and Coast Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1946 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 250-252. System Boards. Jay Street Connecting Railroad
    - Jay Street Connecting Railroad Board of Adjustment, 1955-1959 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-259. System Boards. Chicago and Illinois Midland
    - Chicago and Illinois Midland System Board of Adjustment, 1942-1962 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-261. System Boards. Litchfield and Madison
    - Litchfield and Madison System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1959 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-263. System Boards. Southern Pacific de Mexico
    - Southern Pacific de Mexico System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1955 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 250-268. System Boards. Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern System Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1959 (Box 218, Folder 10)
      March 1958-59.
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 218, Folder 11)
      April 1956-February 1958.
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1956 (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1954 (Box 218, Folder 13)
      July 1951-January 1954.
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1951 (Box 218, Folder 14)
      1921-June 1951.
  - Sub-Series 250-269. System Boards. Tennessee Central
    - Tennessee Central System Board of Adjustment, 1942-1969 (Box 218, Folder 15)
      Disbanded, effective July 1, 1969
  - Sub-Series 250-270. System Boards. Detroit Terminal Railroad
    - Detroit Terminal Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1937-1948 (Box 218, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 250-272. System Boards. Pacific Fruit Express
    - Pacific Fruit Express System Board of Adjustment, 1937-1959 (Box 218, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 250-274. System Boards. Elevator Employees' (Canada)
    - Elevator Employees' (Canada) System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1940 (Box 218, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 250-275. System Boards. Merchants and Miners Transportation
    - Merchants and Miners Transportation System Board of Adjustment, 1930-1942 (Box 218, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 250-286. System Boards. Boston Market Terminal Company Fruit and Produce Handlers
    - Boston Market Terminal Company Fruit and Produce Handlers' System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1968 (Box 218, Folder 20)
    - Boston Market Terminal Company Fruit and Produce Handlers' System Board of Adjustment, 1942-1958 (Box 218, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 250-290. System Boards. Pacific Coast Railroad
    - Pacific Coast Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1928-1930 (Box 218, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 250-301. System Boards. New York and Long Branch Railroad
    - New York and Long Branch Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 250-304. System Boards. Trans-Continental Freight Bureau
    - Trans-Continental Freight Bureau System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1960 (Box 218, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 250-309. System Boards. Meridian Terminal
    - Meridian Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1958 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 250-310. System Boards. Railroad Perishable Inspection Agency Fruit Growers Express
    - Railroad Perishable Inspection Agency Fruit Growers Express System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1965 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Railroad Perishable Inspection Agency Fruit Growers Express System Board of Adjustment, 1941-1956 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-313. System Boards. Rock Island-Frisco Terminal
    - Rock Island-Frisco Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1950-1951 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-315. System Boards. Rutherford Service Company
    - Rutherford Service Company Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 250-328. System Boards. Missouri Pacific Freight Transport
    - Missouri Pacific Freight Transport System Board of Adjustment, 1957 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 250-329. System Boards. Union Motor Coach Terminal Company
    - Union Motor Coach Terminal Company System Board of Adjustment, 1941-1953 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 250-336. System Boards. Detroit and Cleveland Navigation Company
    - Detroit and Cleveland Navigation Company System Board of Adjustment, 1941-1948 (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-337. System Boards. Bamberger Railroad Company
    - Bamberger Railroad Company System Board of Adjustment, 1958 (Box 219, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 250-340. System Boards. Augusta Union Station
    - Augusta Union Station Board of Adjustment, 1950-1952 (Box 219, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-341. System Boards. Parmalee Transportation
    - Parmalee Transportation Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 219, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-351. System Boards. Georgia and Florida
    - Georgia and Florida System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1956 (Box 219, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 250-355. System Boards. East Portland Freight Terminal
    - East Portland Freight Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1949-1966 (Box 219, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 250-363. System Boards. Hannibal Union Depot Terminal
    - Hannibal Union Depot Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1930 (Box 219, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 250-379. System Boards. Goldsboro Union Station
    - Goldsboro Union Station Board of Adjustment, 1955 (Box 219, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 250-384. System Boards. T.F. Quinn and Company
    - T.F. Quinn and Company Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 219, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 250-385. System Boards. Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau
    - Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau Board of Adjustment, 1943-1948 (Box 219, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 250-391. System Boards. Chicago and Calumet River
    - Chicago and Calumet River Board of Adjustment, 1948-1959 (Box 219, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 250-392. System Boards. Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway
    - Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway Board of Adjustment, 1957 (Box 219, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 250-395. System Boards. Chicago Railroad Freight Collection Association
    - Chicago Railroad Freight Collection Association System Board of Adjustment, 1943-1947 (Box 219, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 250-404. System Boards. Manistee and Northeastern
    - Manistee and Northeastern System Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 219, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 250-405. System Boards. Union Passenger Depot Company of Galveston
    - Union Passenger Depot Company of Galveston Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 219, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 250-408. System Boards. Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad
    - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Board of Adjustment, 1947-1952 (Box 219, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 250-410. System Boards. Chicago, Aurora, and Elgin
    - Chicago, Aurora, and Elgin System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1961 (Box 219, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 250-411. System Boards. Tremont and Gulf Railway
    - Tremont and Gulf Railway System Board of Adjustment, 1955 (Box 219, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 250-416. System Boards. Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 219, Folder 26)
      August-October 1965.